Register of the American Relief Administration Russian operational records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Telegrams, 1921-1923
  - Incoming (Box 356)
    - London to New York
      - 1923 January (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 437
    - London and Riga to Washington (Folder 4)
    - Moscow to New York (Box 359, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 438
  - Incoming (extra copies)
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Gorky cable (Folder 3)
    - Ador cable (Folder 4)
  - Outgoing
    - General
      - London and Riga (Folder 5)
      - Yorbon (Folder 6)
      - Yorkham (Folder 7)
      - Yorkrig (Folder 8)
      - Yorkrigmos (Folder 9)
      - Yorkven (Folder 10)
      - Yorkwar (Folder 11)
      - Yorlocon (Folder 12)
      - Yorloham (Folder 13)
      - Yorlomos (Box 360, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 439
      - Yorlorig (Folder 2)
      - Yorloven (Folder 3)
      - Yorlowar (Folder 4)
    - New York to London
      - 1921 July-December (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 440
      - 1922 January-February (Folder 6)
      - 1922 February-March (Box 361, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 441
      - 1922 April-June (Folder 2)
      - 1922 July-September (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 442
      - 1922 October (Box 362, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 443
    - New York to Moscow (Folder 2)
  - Outgoing (extra copies) (Folder 3)
    Available on microfilm reel 444
- Miscellany, circa 1921-1927
  Available on microfilm reels 443-486
  Letters, telegrams, financial records, agreements, reports, summaries, memoranda, insurance claims, clippings, and other printed matter relating to Russian relief, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Accounting file (Box 362)
    - Letters
      - London to New York, 1922 October-December (Folder 4)
      - Moscow
        - To London (Folder 5)
        - To London (Box 363, Folder 1-3)
          Available on microfilm reels 445 and 446
        - To New York (Folder 4)
          Available on microfilm reel 446
      - To Eiduk, RSFSR Representative, 1921 October 10-1922 June 10 (Box 364, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 447
    - Tables and balance sheets. Includes letters (Moscow to New York) (Folder 2-3)
      Available on microfilm reels 447 and 448
  - Food remittance receipts (London to Prag) (Folder 4)
    Available on microfilm reel 448
  - Letters (Box 365, Folder 1-5)
    Available on microfilm reels 449 and 450
  - Letters (Box 366, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 451
  - Memoranda
    - Credit, accounts, bulk sales, etc. (Moscow to New York) (Folder 2)
    - Weights and method of handling claims (Folder 3)
  - Press clippings on Russian relief (Box 367)
    - 1921 May -October (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 452
    - 1921 October -December (Folder 2)
    - 1921 December (Folder 3)
    - 1921 December-1922 February (Folder 4)
    - 1922 February -May (Box 368, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 453
    - 1922 May -June (Folder 2)
    - 1922 June -August (Folder 3)
    - 1922 September-December (Folder 4)
    - 1922 December-1923 March (Box 369, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 454
    - 1923 March -April (Folder 2)
    - 1923 April -June (Folder 3)
    - 1923 June -August (Folder 4)
    - 1923 September-1924 April (Box 370, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 455
    - 1925 January-1926 February (Folder 2)
  - Press releases (Box 371, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 456
  - Printed matter (Folder 2)
  - Subject file
    - Baptists (Folder 3-4)
      Available on microfilm reel 457
    - Catholic relief organizations (Box 372, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 458
    - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America (Folder 2)
    - Goldman, Emma, articles on Russia, New York World, 1922 March 26 -April 4 (Folder 3)
    - History and policy (Folder 4)
    - Latvia (Folder 5)
    - Lithuania (Folder 6)
    - London Office
      - Letters and telegrams
        - 1922 March 4 -April 15 (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 459
        - 1922 April 17 -June 6 (Folder 8)
        - 1923 April 3 -July (Box 373, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 460
      - Press reports, 1922 August-September (Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous - Closing (Folder 3)
    - Lutherans
      - Lutheran Council (Folder 4)
      - Relief organizations (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 461
    - Market prices (Folder 6)
    - Medical Division. Monthly medical and sanitary reports (Box 374)
      - 1922 August (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 462
      - 1922 September (Folder 2)
      - 1922 October (Folder 3)
      - 1922 November (Folder 4)
      - 1922 December (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 463
      - 1923 January (Folder 6)
      - 1923 February (Folder 7)
      - 1923 March (Folder 8)
      - 1923 April (Box 375, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 464
    - Mennonites
      - 1921 September 6-1922 June 29 (Folder 2)
      - 1922 July 2-1923 May 12 (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 465
    - Moscow News Items, 1921 September 15-1922 November 27 (Box 376, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 466
    - Moscow Office
      - General
        - Accounting file. Cables and miscellany (Folder 2)
        - Agreements, budgets, cash audits, etc. (Folder 3-5)
          Available on microfilm reel 467
        - Letters (Box 377)
          - Incoming
            - General (Folder 1-2)
              Available on microfilm reel 468
            - Lander, RSFSR Representative, 1921 November-1923 July (Folder 3)
              Available on microfilm reel 469
            - London, 1921-1922 (Folder 4)
            - London, 1921-1922 (Box 378, Folder 1)
              Available on microfilm reel 470
          - Outgoing
            - Dickinson, T. (History Department representative) (Folder 2)
            - Lander, RSFSR Representative
              - General, 1922-1923 (Folder 3-5)
                Available on microfilm reels 470 and 471
              - Insurance claims (Box 379, Folder 1-2)
                Available on microfilm reel 472
            - State Bank, 1922-1923 (Folder 3-4)
              Available on microfilm reel 473
        - Letters and cables with districts, 1922 (Box 380, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 474
        - Messages, Outgoing, 1921-1922 (Folder 2)
        - Telegrams
          - Incoming (Folder 3-4)
          - Incoming (Box 381, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 475
          - Incoming and outgoing (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 476
          - Outgoing (Folder 3)
          - Outgoing (Box 382, Folder 1-2)
            Available on microfilm reel 477
      - Finance and Accounting Division, 1922-1923
        - General (Folder 3-6)
          Available on microfilm reels 477 and 478
        - Joint Distribution Committee. Letters, 1922-1923 (Box 383, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 479
      - Supply Division
        - American Friends Service Committee (Folder 2)
        - American Mennonite Relief (Folder 3)
        - Baptists (Folder 4)
        - Friends International Service (Folder 5)
        - Joint Distribution Committee (Folder 6)
        - National Catholic Welfare Council (Folder 7)
        - National Lutheran Welfare Council (Folder 8)
        - Volga Relief Society (Folder 9)
        - Young Men's Christian associations (Folder 10)
    - National Lutheran Council. See Lutherans
    - New York Office
      - General
        - Accounting and accountability file (Folder 11)
        - Cables
          - General, 1921-1923 (Folder 12-13)
          - General, 1921-1923 (Box 384, Folder 1-4)
            Available on microfilm reel 480
          - International Red Cross, 1922 February (Folder 5)
          - Publicity (Folder 6-7)
          - Volga Relief Society (Folder 8)
          - Miscellaneous (Folder 9)
        - Letters of thanks (Folder 10)
      - American Red Cross, 1922-1924 (Folder 11)
      - Commodities - Fish (Folder 12)
      - Insurance claims (Folder 13)
      - Purchasing Commission (Box 385)
        - Letters, 1921-1922 (Folder 1-3)
          Available on microfilm reel 481
        - Minutes (Folder 4)
        - Records (Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
      - Refugees, 1922-1923 (Folder 7)
      - Repatriation, 1922-1923 (Folder 8)
      - Russian Red Cross, 1922-1923 (Folder 9)
      - Shipping (Box 386)
        - Insurance Advisry Committee (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 482
        - Reports, 1921-1923 (Folder 2-5)
      - Transportation, 1922 April-May (Folder 6)
      - U.S. Grain Corporation - Liquidation (Folder 7)
      - Ukrainian personnel, 1922 (Folder 8)
      - Ukrainian relief (Folder 9)
    - Northwest Russia (General IUdenich) (Folder 10)
    - Novorossisk (Box 387, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 483
    - Odessa (Folder 2)
    - Ports
      - Reports (Folder 3-4)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 5)
    - Prague Office. Letters, 1922-1923 (Folder 6-7)
    - Riga Office
      - Finance and accounting file (William McGuire), 1922-1923 (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 484
      - Letters, 1921-1922 (Folder 9)
      - Telegrams and letters, 1923 February-July (Folder 10)
    - Ringland, Arthur C. (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - Student Friendship Fund (Folder 2)
    - United States Shipping Board Emergency Fleet Corporation, 1922 January-1924 October (Folder 3)
    - Volga Relief Society (Folder 4-5)
      Available on microfilm reels 484 and 485
    - Young Men's Christian associations (Folder 6)
      Available on microfilm reel 485
    - Young Women's Christian associations (Folder 7)
  - Miscellany. Reports, sales logs, statistics, press releases, clippings, and other printed matter, 1921-1927 (Box 389-394.)
    Available on microfilm reel 486
- Photographs, circa 1921-1923
  Circa 5,000 prints and 2,300 negatives of photographs taken by the A.R.A., arranged into categories and by geographic area thereunder.
  - General (Box 395)
    - 73 prints depicting A.R.A. personnel and associates, including Bernard J. Beard, Henry Beeuwkey, Walter Bell, Harold Blandy, Carleton Bowden, Elmer Burbank, George Becker Cormick, Walter Davenport, John H. Dawson, Emil Dodge, Harry Fink, F. H. Fowcar, Edward Fox, W. C. Garner, J. P. Goodrich, William Grove, George P. Harrington, Henry Haskell, Piet Hein Hofstra, Lincoln Hutchinson, William R. Kearney, Jr., William J. Kelly, Tracy Kohl, John J. Mangan, George N. McClintock, Theophilus Meyer, Dr. Morehead, C. S. Morris, George Poppoff, Cyril J. C. Guinn, Evan Renshaw, George Repp, Caroline Klein Robbins, Dr. Rollins, Philip B. Sheild, Charles Talford, Floyd Traynham, Herschel C. Walker, James B. Walsh (Folder A)
    - 24 prints depicting A.R.A. staff and offices (Folder B)
    - 13 prints depicting personnel and associates (Folder C)
    - 10 prints depicting mainly the May Day parade of 1922 reviewed by Leon Trotsky (Folder D)
    - 95 prints depicting scenes in Russian cities, including Feodosia, Kazan, Saratov, Simbirsk, Simferopol; Ukrainian cities; Ufa; Tsaritsyn; Vechrova (Folder E)
    - 63 prints depicting scenes in various Russian cities (Folder F)
    - 24 prints depicting street scenes in various Russian cities (Folder G)
    - 32 prints depicting Russian children (Folder H)
    - 26 prints depicting Russian refugees in Russia (Folder I)
    - 29 prints depicting famine victims (Folder J)
    - 21 prints depicting Russian railroads (Folder K)
    - 12 prints depicting ships (Folder L)
    - 15 prints depicting warehouses (Folder M)
    - 36 prints depicting transporting supplies on camel, etc. (Folder N)
    - 72 prints depicting medical care for famine victims (Box 396, Folder O)
    - 26 prints depicting a hospital, school, and orphanage, named after Harold Blandy (Folder P)
    - 42 prints depicting A.R.A. kitchens in various cities (Folder Q)
    - 27 prints depicting corn distribution in Simbirsk (Folder R)
    - 29 prints depicting food distribution paid by remittances (Folder S)
    - 11 prints depicting farms (Folder T)
    - 23 prints depicting reconstruction (Folder U)
    - 58 prints depicting miscellaneous subjects (Folder V)
    - 2 prints depicting William N. Haskell and staff (Folder W)
    - 6 prints depicting the Herbert Hoover Hospital in Odessa (Folder X)
    - 3 prints depicting ARA officials O. J. Anderson, Walter L. Bell, Piet Hein Hofstra, George N. McClintock, William C. Shaffroth, Mr. Solonov (Folder Y)
    - 10 prints depicting the port of Novorossisk (Folder Z)
  - Official photographic history of the A.R.A.'s relief operations in Russia (3,846 prints taken by A.R.A. photographers Floyd Traynham and Nellie E. Gardner) (Box 397)
    - General. Original subject index entitled "Pictorial History of Russian Famine Relief," compiled by Harrison Meserole. Includes an introduction by Sharon McGuiness, 1978 (Folder 1)
    - Prints
      - #1 Childfeeding (23 prints)
        - Moscow (Folder 2)
        - Crimea, Kazan, Minsk, Petrograd, Samara, Saratov, Simbirsk, Tsaritsyn (Folder 3)
        - Ufa (Folder 4)
        - Ukraine (Folder 5)
        - Unidentified locations (Folder 6)
      - #2 Medical relief (264 prints) (Box 398)
        - Kazan, Minsk, Moscow, Samara, Simbirsk, Orenburg (Folder 1)
        - Petrograd (Folder 2)
        - Saratov (Folder 3)
        - Ufa (Folder 4)
        - Ukraine (Folder 5)
        - Unidentified locations (Folder 6)
      - #3 Transportation (337 prints) (Box 399)
        - Automobiles (Folder 1)
        - Livestock (Folder 2)
        - Moscow and Petrograd (Folder 3)
        - Port operations (Folder 4)
        - Railroads (Folder 5)
        - River (Folder 6)
        - Warehouse operations (Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Volga-Ural region (Kazan, Samara, Saratov, Tsaritsyn, Ufa., etc.) (Folder 8)
          - Ukraine, European parts (Folder 9)
      - #4 Relief of the intelligentsia (54 prints) - Crimea, Kiev, Moscow, Petrograd, Simbirsk, Ufa, unidentified locations (Box 400, Folder 1)
      - #5 Reconstruction (64 prints) - Ufa, Ukraine, miscellaneous locations (Folder 2)
      - #6 Remittances (207 prints)
        - Food remittances
          - Contents and documents (Folder 3)
          - Packing boxes, warehouses (Folder 4)
          - Recipients and delivery (Folder 5)
        - Clothing remittances
          - Contents, packing boxes, warehouses (Folder 6)
          - Recipients and delivery (Folder 7)
      - #7 Corn distribution (85 prints) - New York, Novorossisk, Odessa, Samara, Simbirsk, Tsaritsyn (Box 401, Folder 1)
      - #8 Buildings used by the A.R.A. (20 prints)
        - Samara, Saratov, Tsaritsyn, Ufa (Folder 2)
        - Crimea, Kazan, Simbirsk, Ukraine (Folder 3)
        - Minsk, Moscow, Petrograd, warehouses, and unidentified locations (Folder 4)
      - #9 Notable Russian buildings (115 prints)
        - Moscow (Folder 5)
        - Petrograd (Folder 6)
        - Crimea, Kazan, Saratov, Simbirsk, Ufa, Ukraine (Folder 7)
      - #10 Schools and children's homes (133 prints) (Box 402)
        - Crimea, Kazan, Moscow, Odessa, Samara, Saratov, Simbirsk, Tsaritsyn, unidentified locations (Folder 1)
        - Ufa (Folder 2)
      - #11 Personnel (356 prints). See appendices B and C for partial list of names
        - Crimea, Kazan, Samara, Saratov, Simbirsk, Tsaritsyn, Ukraine, unidentified locations (Folder 3)
        - Russian officials and Russian employees of the A.R.A. (Folder 4)
        - Minsk, Moscow, Petrograd (Box 403, Folder 1)
        - Ufa (Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 3)
      - #12 Antiquities (13 prints) - Crimea, Ufa (Folder 4)
      - #13 Types of Russian people (181 prints) (Box 404)
        - General, Moscow, Simbirsk, Ufa (Folder 1)
        - Crimea, Kazan, Petrograd, Samara, Saratov, Tsaritsyn, Ukraine, miscellaneous locations (Folder 2)
      - #14 Harold F. Blandy's funeral (22 prints) - Moscow (Folder 3)
      - #15 Horrors (195 prints)
        - General, Tsaritsyn, Ufa, Ukraine (Folder 4)
        - Crimea, Kazan, Petrograd, Samara, Saratov, miscellaneous (Folder 5)
        - Unidentified locations (Folder 6)
        - Album (Box 562)
      - #16 Russian livestock (23 prints) - Crimea, Moscow, Samara, Ufa, Ukraine, unidentified locations (Box 405, Folder 1)
      - #17 Demonstrations of appreciation, parties, and celebrations (26 prints) - Kazan, Petrograd, Samara, Ufa, Ukraine, Volga River (Folder 2)
      - #18 Russian funerals and cemetaries (15 prints) - Crimea, Moscow, Tsaritsyn, Ufa, Ukraine (Folder 3)
      - #19 Homes of Russian people (19 prints) - Crimea, Simbirsk, Ufa, Ukraine, unidentified locations (Folder 4)
      - #20 Russian clergy (12 prints) - Tsaritsyn, Ufa (Folder 5)
      - #21 Red troops, May Day 1922 etc. (74 prints). See appendix C for partial list of names - Crimea, Moscow, Petrograd, Simbirsk, Ufa, Ukraine, unidentified locations (Folder 6)
      - #22 United States Navy (11 prints) - Crimea, Hamburg, New York, Petrograd, Ukraine (Folder 7)
      - #23 Destruction and decay (28 prints) - Crimea, Moscow, Petrograd, Simbirsk, Ufa, Ukraine, Volga River (Folder 8)
      - #24 Markets, market places, shops, beggars, etc. (60 prints) - Crimea, Moscow, Petrograd, Samara, Saratov, Simbirsk, Ufa, Ukraine, unidentified locations (Box 406, Folder 1)
      - #25 Refugees, waifs, etc. (283 prints)
        - Crimea (Folder 2)
        - Minsk, Moscow, Orel, Petrograd, Samara, Saratov, Simbirsk, Ufa, White Russia (Folder 3)
        - Ukraine (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified locations (Folder 5)
      - #26 Miscellaneous (520 prints) (Box 407)
        - Saratov (Folder 1)
        - Petrograd (Folder 2)
        - Crimea (Folder 3)
        - Ukraine (Folder 4)
        - Unidentified locations and Russian cartoons (Folder 5)
        - Moscow (Box 408, Folder 1)
        - Simbirsk (Folder 2)
        - Ufa/Miass Siberia (Folder 3)
        - Kazan, Samara, Tsaritsyn, miscellaneous locations (Folder 4)
      - Unsorted (Box 409)
    - Negatives (numbers refer to red numbers written on the prints to locate the desired negative) (Box 410)
      - 1-1250
      - 1251-2300 (Box 411)
- Material Transferred from the American Relief Administration European Operational Records
- Russian Famine Relief, Office File, 1921-1923
  Background material re policy and operations of the A.R.A. in the Soviet Union, including its establishment and withdrawal from the Soviet Union, correspondence of various offices of the A.R.A., personnel file, and reports of district supervisors re field conditions, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - General. Background, policy and operation of the ARA in the Soviet Union
    - General
      - General, including history and policy of operation and work of other relief groups (Box 412, Folder 1-4)
        Available on microfilm reel 487
      - Clippings and excerpts from newspapers re situation in Soviet Union before arrival of ARA (Folder 5-6)
        Available on microfilm reels 487 and 488
      - Survey of economic conditions (Folder 7)
        Available on microfilm reel 488
    - Continuation of operations (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Establishment of Russian relief
      - Chronology (Folder 2)
      - Plan of operations (Folder 3)
    - Inspection Division, consolidated monthly report of relief activities (Folder 4)
    - List of districts suffering from famine (Folder 5)
    - Memoranda, Inter-office (Folder 6)
    - Purchasing Commission file
      - General
        - General. Includes correspondence, documentary material, memoranda and financial reports (Folder 7)
        - Final settlement (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 489
        - Minutes of meetings (Folder 9)
      - Arcos purchases (Folder 10)
      - Livingston file (Folder 11)
      - Stock exchange (Folder 12)
    - Statistical records (Box 414, Folder 1)
    - Summaries of operation (Folder 2)
    - Questionnaire re cause of famine (Folder 3-4)
    - Withdrawal and liquidation
      - General (Folder 5-10)
        Available on microfilm reels 489 and 490
      - Haskell Dinner (Box 415, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 490
      - Visit of Soviet official (Folder 2)
  - Clippings (Folder 3)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - General (Folder 4-6)
      - A-B (Folder 7)
        Available on microfilm reel 491
      - C-E (Folder 8)
      - F (Folder 9)
      - K (Folder 10)
      - L (Folder 11)
      - M (Folder 12)
      - P-R (Folder 13)
      - S (Folder 14)
      - T (Folder 15)
    - Banks (Box 416, Folder 1)
    - Chicherin, Georgii (Folder 2)
    - Eiduk, Aleksandr (Folder 3)
  - European Children's Fund (Folder 4)
    - European offices
      - Constantinople (Folder 5)
      - Danzig (Folder 6)
      - Hamburg (Folder 7-9)
        Available on microfilm reels 491 and 492
      - Kiev (Folder 10)
        Available on microfilm reel 492
      - Libau (Folder 11)
      - Moscow (Folder 12)
      - Novorossiisk (Folder 13)
      - Odessa (Folder 14)
      - Petrograd (Folder 15)
      - Reval (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - Riga (Folder 2-3)
      - Warsaw (Folder 4)
    - Harding, Warren (Folder 5)
    - New York Office. Cablegrams (Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Alonzo (Folder 7)
  - Personnel file. Correspondence related to tours of Russia
    - Fisher, Harold (Folder 8)
    - Flesh, E. (Folder 9)
    - Rickard, Edgar (Folder 10)
    - Herter, Christian (Folder 11)
      Available on microfilm reel 493
  - Reports
    - General
      - General - Reports to President Warren G. Harding (Folder 12)
      - Committee to Collect Information on Russia, report to British Parliament (Folder 13)
      - Fisher, Harold, American Relief Administration Russian Negotiations, 1919-1921 (Folder 14)
      - Hoover, Herbert, The Russian Relief Situation (Folder 15)
      - Kamenev, Lev, report on Russian crops (Folder 16)
      - Kennedy, J. A., "American Relief Administration Operations in Russia" (Folder 17)
    - Agriculture and stock raising (Box 418, Folder 1)
    - Children, Physical condition of (Folder 2)
    - Clothing needs (Folder 3)
    - Commodities (Folder 4)
    - Field conditions
      - General - "Moscow's Weekly Letter", 1922
        - February (Folder 5)
        - March (Folder 6)
        - April (Folder 7)
        - May (Folder 8)
        - June (Folder 9)
        - July (Folder 10)
        - August (Folder 11)
        - September (Folder 12)
      - Allen, Ronald (Folder 13)
      - Barringer, T. (Folder 14)
      - Beeuwkes, Henry. Includes final report on medical mission (Folder 15)
      - Bell, W. Includes letters of gratitude from Russian children (Folder 16)
        Available on microfilm reel 494
      - Blomquist, Alvin (Folder 17)
      - Botkowski (Folder 18)
    - Bowden, C. (Folder 19)
      - Brace, Blanche (Folder 20)
      - Brink, H. (Folder 21)
      - Buckley, Harold (Folder 22)
      - Burland, Elmer (Folder 23)
      - Callahan, Edgar (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - Carrol, Philip (Folder 2)
      - Childs, J. Rivers (Folder 3)
      - Clapp, Paul (Folder 4)
      - Cocoran, A. (Folder 5)
      - Coleman, W. (Folder 6)
      - Davenport, W. (Folder 7)
      - Davis, W. (Folder 8)
      - Dear, W. (Folder 9)
      - Driscoll, G. (Folder 10)
      - Flesh, Edward (Folder 11)
      - Floete, Carl (Folder 12)
      - Forbes, C. (Folder 13)
      - Foster, Theodore (Folder 14)
      - Fox, Edward (Folder 15)
      - Franklin, Curtis (Folder 16)
      - Gill, Everett (Folder 17)
      - Godfrey, M. (Folder 18)
      - Goodrich, G. (Folder 19)
      - Gregg, John (Folder 20)
      - Harrington, George (Folder 21)
      - Hofstra, P. (Folder 22)
      - Hutchinson, Lincoln (Folder 23)
        Available on microfilm reel 495